ARTYOM ZAGOSKIN

iOS Developer

in https://linkedin.com/in/artyomzagoskin

https://github.com/Inxel

artyzago@gmail.com

Open-minded, flexible, mindfulness, collaborative iOS developer with 4+ years of experience. Participate in all phases of development: system design, UI and UX discussion, decomposition and development. Spending spare time exploring new technologies to use it in pet and work projects. Fascinated about my job.

LANGUAGES

English

Professional Working Proficiency

Russian

Native

CERTIFICATES

iOS Development

Napoleon IT Course 2019

FCE (CEFR Level - B2)

Cambridge University Press 2019

SKILLS

- Swift
- SwiftUI
- · Multi-threading
- Object-Oriented Programming
- Protocol-Oriented Programming
- Collaboration
- Communication
- · Time management
- · Agile and Scrum workflow
- JIRA / Confluence / Git

EDUCATION

Computer and Information Sciences

South Ural State University

2017 - 2021

WORK EXPERIENCE

iOS Engineer

2021 - present

Aviasales

The leading travel metasearch company in Eastern Europe and Central Asia (with more then 15 mln unique users monthly).

- Develop brand-new hotel page and hotels search (75% more bookings)
- Worked with results page (results showing 1.5x faster) and ticket screen
- Make UI with SwiftUI (previously UIKit without storyboards)
- Objective-C to Swift refactoring
- Work in team of 4 iOS developers
- MVVM architecture
- Code review
- Unit and snapshot tests
- Interviewer

iOS Engineer

2019 - 2021

Napoleon IT

- 1. Retail app:
- Clean Swift (VIP) architecture
- Worked in team of 2 iOS developers
- Developed catalog, authorization, shop cart, etc.
- 2. Platform for local services and specialized jobs:
 - VIPER architecture
 - Developed task creating constructor, transactions history, etc.
 - Localization
- Only one iOS developer
- 3. Initialization of app (MVVM + Coordinators).
- 4. Mentor.
- 5. Napoleon IT iOS course lecturer.